

## **NGUYEN VAN A**

## **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and for laying out page content, and other word proces of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

## **EDUCATION**



## **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. ently occur that pleasures have administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

## **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

## Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult kham: "But I m and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

## Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to ears old. Richard McClintock, a La goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute

**ACTIVITIES** 



Sep 2003 - 2007

#### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer will give you a complete account of the system, and expound the actual 'queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

## HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US es and owing to the claims of duty or the

#### **REFERENCES**



## **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

## **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

## **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt eople to focus on his fonts, to ima and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities